RG 058, Research Commission
Connecticut State Library
- Series 1. Project applications, 1965-1971
  - P-181, University of Connecticut, Biological degradation of thatch in turf, Granted 1969 March 13 (Box 3)
  - P-182, New England Institute, Effects of radio frequency fields on the sedimentation rates of suspensoids, granted 1968 December 20 (Box 3)
  - P-183, University of Connecticut, Depth distribution of living foraminifers around pollutant producing isntallations in coastal Connecticut, Declined 1968 December 20 (Box 3)
  - P-184, IFF, Long-range technological and evonomic developments, Granted 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-185, University of Connecticut, Vitamen E from the lipids of alfalfa, Declined 1968 November 15 (Box 3)
  - P-186, University of Connecticut, Content analysis of judicial decisions, Declined 1968 December 20 (Box 3)
  - P-187, University of Bridgeport, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-188, Yale University, Modular, prefabricated housing feasiblity study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-189, Nathan Associates, Modyular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-190, Arthur D. Little, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-191, Urban Design Associates, Modular, prefabricated housing, feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-192, University of Hartford, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-193, Social Planning Associates, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-194, OSTI, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-195, Travelers Research Center, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-196, Rouse Activities, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-197, Environmental Research Foundation, Modular, prefabricated housing feasibility study, Declined 1968 August 16 (Box 3)
  - P-198, Yale University, Incorporating Leed and Auguer Emission Facilities in apparatus for study of solid surfaces, Granted, 1968 Decmber 20 (Box 3)
  - P-199, Trinity College, Coordinate concepts for handling grievances of ghetto residents, Declined 1968 November 15 (Box 3)
  - P-200, Yale University, Growth, structure and properties of surface oxides, Granted 1968 December 20 (Box 3)
  - P-201, University of Connecticut, Identification of consumer resources in Connecticut, Greanted 1968 December 20 (Box 3)
  - P-202, University of Hartford, Collection and disposal of abandoned motor vehicles, Granted 1968 December 20 (Box 3)
  - P-203, Resource engineering Associates, Inc., Metal finishing wastes in municipal systems, Granted 1969 June 27 (Box 3)
  - P-204, Yale University, Growth & development of codium fragile from Long Island Sound, Provisional 1969 September 18 (Box 3)
  - P-205, Newington Children's Hospital, Patient flow to a regional children's hospital, Deferred 1968 December 20, Declined 1969 May 8 (Box 3)
  - P-206, Simpson and Curtin, Complementary transportation needs (Box 3)
  - P-207, Wilbur Smith & Associates, Complementary transportation needs, Contract voted 1969 April 10 (Box 3)
  - P-208, W. C. Gilman & Co., Inc., Complementary transportation needs (Box 3)
  - P-209, Wesleyan University, Organic electrochemical instrumentation, Granted 1969 June 27 (Box 3)
  - P-210, University of Connecticut, Slow flow of variable property gas, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 3)
  - P-211, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Effect of diet on the mechanical properties of bone, Withdrawn 1969 June 16 (Box 3)
  - P-212, Child & Family Services of Connecticut, Use of counseling services by adoptive and natural parents (Box 3)
  - P-213, University of Connecticut, Diseases of Fish in the Quinebaug and Thames Rivers, Granted 1969 June 27 (Box 3)
  - P-214, UAC Resarch Labs, Airport research for air freight, Granted 1969 February 13 (Box 3)
  - P-215, TRC, Cloud seeding experiments, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 3)
  - P-216, University of Connecticut, Vortex formation in liquid draining from cylindrical tank, Declined 1969 July 10 (Box 3)
  - P-217, Yale University, Photosynthesis, translocation and dry matter production, Withdrawn 1969 May 29 (Box 4)
  - P-218, Wesleyan University, Sensitive thermometer based on measurement of thermal noise, Granted 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-219, University of Connecticut, Seismic response and stability of spherical structure-foundation systems submerged in fluid media, Declined 1969 July 10 (Box 4)
  - P-220, Yale University, Determinants of firm outlays on capital investment, R & D, advertising, mergers & dividends, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-221, University of Connecticut, Biochemistry of animal and human brain in normal and diseased states, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-222, Hartford Hospital, Neurochemistry of multiple sclerosis, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-223. Yale University, Rising bubbles in liquids, Granted 1969 August 14 (Box 4)
  - P-224, Yale University, Incident light in forest sunflecks, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-225, University of Hartford, Support request to strengthen acoustics education, Granted 19790 July 9 (Box 4)
  - P-226, University of Hartford, Urban generalist: A manpower need for Connecticut, Granted 1969 May 8 (Box 4)
  - P-227, University of Connecticut, Federal income-maintenance plans, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-228, Effects of chemical pollutants on organic composition of estuarine molluscs, Conditional award 1969 May 8 (Box 4)
  - P-229, University of Connecticut, Scanning electron microscope, Granted 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-230, Child & Family Services, Teaching severely distrurbed youngsters sixty work sight vocabulary, Granted 1969 May 8 (Box 4)
  - P-231, Meyers Electro/Cooling Products, Research & evaluation for rat control programs, Contract voted 1969 May 8 (Box 4)
  - P-232, University of Hartford, Evaluation of tax base equalization method of allocating state funds to municipalities, Declined 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-233, Yale University, Subunit association of hemoglobin, Declined 1969 July 10 (Box 4)
  - P-234, Travelers Research Corporation, Air pollution information and analysis system, Conditional award made 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-235, Quinnipiac College, Urban generalist, Declined 1969 May 8 (Box 4)
  - P-236, Debell & Richardson, Chemical modification of scrap rubber, Granted 1969 June 27 (Box 4)
  - P-237, Haskins Laboratories, Computer facilities for experimenting with speech, Granted 1969 August 14 (Box 4)
  - P-238, Yale University, Dynamic problems in solids using ultra high speed photography, Granted 1969 October (Box 4)
  - P-239, Dept. of Mental Health, A twin study of creatuivity, Granted 1969 September 18 (Box 4)
  - P-240, URIC, Development and publication of Connecticut Research news medium, Declined 1969 August 14 (Box 4)
  - P-241, University of Connecticut, Editing the papers of Jonathan Trumbull, Sr., Granted, 1970 January 8 (Box 4)
  - P-242, Albertus Magnus College, Transferability of government operations to nongovernmental sector, Declined 1969 September 18 (Box 4)
  - P-243, Yale University, Reecording microdensitometer for spectroscopic research, Declined 1969 October 9 (Box 4)
  - P-244, Puerto Rican Human Resources Foundation, Survey of Puerto Rican population of the City of New Haven, Granted 1969 August 14 (Box 4)
  - P-245, Travelers Research Corporation, Watershed characteristics, Granted 1969 December 22 (Box 4)
  - P-246, University of Connecticut, Pesticides and man, Granted 1969 December 24 (Box 4)
  - P-247, URIC, Connecticut research mobility, Declined 1969 October 9 (Box 4)
  - P-248, Yale University, Electron spectroscopy of crystal surfaces, Granted 1970 February 12 (Box 4)
  - P-249, Institute for the Future, Social indicators for Connecticut, Granted 1969 October 9 (Box 4)
  - P-250, Barnes Engineering Co., Remote measurement of air pollutants, Granted 1970 February 12 (Box 4)
  - P-251, University of Connecticut, Health care among north end residents, Declined 1969 September 18 (Box 4)
  - P-252, Wesleyan University, Mass spectrometry, Declined 1969 September 18 (Box 4)
  - P-253, Information Services of Connecticut, Information service for Connecticut researchers, Declined 1969 September 18 (Box 4)
  - P-254, Wesleyan University, Spinner magnetometer and magnetic susceptibility bridge, Granted 1970 February 25 (Box 4)
  - P-255, Yale UNiversity, Analysis of demand for outing-type recreation in Connecticut State Parks, Granted (Box 4)
  - P-256, University of Connecticut, Clinical organ transplantation, Deferred action 1970 April 9 (Box 4)
  - P-257, University of Connecticut, Inelastic atom-atom collisions, Granted 1970 February 12 (Box 4)
  - P-258, URIC, Connecticut Patent Registry, Declined 1969 November 13 (Box 4)
  - P-259, TRC, Identification and assistance of children with perceptual learning disabilities, Granted 1970 February 25 (Box 4)
  - P-260, Yale University, Enzyme activation, Granted 1970 February 12 (Box 4)
  - P-261, Talcott Mountain Science Center, Seismic activity, Granted 1970 June 11 (Box 4)
  - P-262, University of Connecticut, Heat transfer of an impinging jet with crossflow, Declined 1970 April 9 (Box 4)
  - P-263, University of Connecticut, ETV in consumer education, Declined 1970 January 15 (Box 4)
  - P-264, Universiyt of Hartford, Application of electonics to music, Declined 1970 February 12 (Box 4)
  - P-265, Yale University, Lithium and human aggression, Declined 1970 April 9 (Box 4)
  - P-266, Mental Health Dept., Mental Health Planning Council, Withdrawn 1970 April 1 (Box 4)
  - P-267, Mount Sinai Hospital, Computer diagnosis of pulmonary embolism, Declined 1970 May 21 (Box 4)
  - P-268, University of Connecticut, Computer search tapes from ASM, Granted 1970 February 12 (Box 4)
  - P-269, University of Connecticut, Water waste disposal systems, Granted 1970 May 21 (Box 4)
  - P-270, University of Connecticut, Heat transfer and turbulence in impinging jets, Declined 1970 April 9 (Box 4)
  - P-271, Yale University, Dry matter production, Granted 1970 June 11 (Box 4)
  - P-272, Aquarand, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-273, Parsons, Brinckerhoff, Quade & Douglas, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-274, Swindell-Dressler Company, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-275, Containerport Development Corporation, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-276, Booz, Allen Applied Research, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-277, Battelle Northwest, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-278, TRAC, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 4)
  - P-279, Goodkind & O'Dea, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
    This file is not present.
  - P-280, Tippets-Abbett-McCarthy, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-281, Resource Engineering Associates, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-282, Wilbur Smith & Associates, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-283, Advanced Technolog Consultants, Corporation, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-284, EBS Management Consultants, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-285, The Ralph M. Parsons Co., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-286, Peat, Marwich, Mitchell, & Co., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-287, Frederic R. Harris, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-288, UARL, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-289, TRC and Muller, Fox and Pennington, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-290, Soros Associates, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Contract awarded (Box 5)
  - P-291, A. T. Kearney & Company, New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-292, Anatech, Inc., New concepts in seaports, Declined (Box 5)
  - P-293, University of Bridgeport, Ecological study of Housatonic River (Box 5)
  - P-294, Child & Family Services, Group psychotheraphy with children, Granted 1970 May 21 (Box 5)
  - P-295, Shellfish Laboratories, Scallop culture, Granted 1970 May 21 (Box 5)
  - P-296, University of Connecticut, Perfused kidney's transfer function, Granted 1970 June 11 (Box 5)
  - P-297, Meyers Electro/Cooling Products, Inc., Refuse storage depository system, Granted 1970 July 9 (Box 5)
  - P-298, Center for the Environment and Man, Inc. (TRC), Simulation of estuarine processes, Partially granted 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-299, Trinity College, Feedback sleep/waking processes, Granted 1970 July 9 (Box 5)
  - P300, Yale University, Plant communities adjacent to highways, Granted 1970 May 21 (Box 5)
  - P-301, Institute for the Future, Forecasting social indicators, Granted 1970 June 11, Bond Commission declined 1970 July 16 (Box 5)
  - P-302, University of Connecticut, Coastal upwelling, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 5)
  - P-303, University of Connecticut, Intelligent artificial teacher, Granted 1970 July 9 (Box 5)
  - P-304, Fairfield University, High school students' attitudes, Granted 1970 May 21 (Box 5)
  - P-305, University of Connecitcut, Social science data center, Granted 1970 July 9 (Box 5)
  - P-306, center for the Environment & Man, Municipal function computerization, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-307, James S. Minges & Associates, Community environmental study, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-308, Yale University, Attenuation of solar beam, Granted 1970 July 9 (Box 5)
  - P-309, University of Connecticut, Transient response in structural members, Declined 1970 September 10 (Box 5)
  - P-310, University of Connecticut, Puerto-Rican community in Hartford, Declined 1970 May 21 (Box 5)
  - P-311, University of Hartford, The Puerto Rican worker, Granted 1970 May 21 (Box 5)
  - P-312, University of Connecticut, Vibrations of trapezoidal plates, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-313, URIC, Environmental science information center, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-314, University of Connecticut, Socialization of student, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-315, University of Connecitcut, Nuclear power plant waste heat removal, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-316, Time Share Corp., Computer information handling system -- General Assembly -- II (Box 5)
  - P-317, Computer Assistance, Inc., Computer information handling system -- General Assembly -- I and II (Box 5)
  - P-318, COMTROL, Computer information handling system -- General Assembly -- I and II (Box 5)
  - P-319, IBM Corp., Computer information handling system -- General Assembly -- I and II (Box 5)
  - P-320, Keane Associates, Computer information handling system -- General Assembly -- I and II (Box 5)
  - P-321, Number Nine, Inc., Number Nine: A social experiment, Granted 1970 June 11 (Box 5)
  - P-322, UARL, Demand-Actuated Bus Operation, 1970 August 4 (Box 5)
  - P-323, CBS Labs, Sound attenuation, 1970 September 10 (Box 5)
  - P-324, University of Connecticut, Interactions of electrons with single crystals, Granted 1970 July 9 (Box 5)
  - P-325, University of Connecticut, Biobehavioral effects of polluted air, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-326, University of Connecticut, Impinging jet in a cross flow, Declined 1970 October 27 (Box 5)
  - P-327, University of Connecticut, Essential oils I and II, Granted 1970 November 12 (Box 5)
  - P-328, Yale University, Laser-Raman analysis of air pollutants, Declined 1970 August 13 (Box 5)
  - P-329, UARL, Geasibility of COGAS power stations, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 5)
  - P-330, Educational Research Associates, Research needs in public schools, Declined 1970 September 10 (Box 5)
  - P-331, University of Connecticut, Philosophy of futures, Superseded by P-340 (Box 5)
  - P-332, Yale University, Approaches to tobacco improvement, Declined 1970 September 10 (Box 5)
  - P-333, University of Connecticut, Glucocorticoid hormones, Granted 1970 September 10 (Box 5)
  - P-334, Yale University, Lockwood-Mathews Mansion Museum, Granted 1970 September 10 (Box 5)
  - P-335, Center for the Environment and Man, Inc., Connecticut rainfall study, Granted 1970 August 13 (Box 6)
  - P-336, University of Connecticut, Neuromorphology program, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-337, Welson & Company, Inc., Firefighter protective clothing, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-338, University of Connecticut, Biochemical mutations in tobacco, Declined 1970 Septermber 10 (Box 6)
  - P-339, University of Bridgeport, Determination of mophinoid alkaloids, Declined 1970 November 12 (Box 6)
  - P-340, University of Connecticut, Dynamics of a creative society, Declined 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-341, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Theoretical soil mechanics, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-342, Yale University, Removal of organic compounds from effluents, Withdrawn 1970 November 3 (Box 6)
  - P-343, Association for the Study of Conecticut History, Journal of Connecticut History, Declined 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-344, White Memorial Foundation, Algae control in eutrophying lakes, Declined 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-345, Trinity College, Pre-professionals in public administration, Granted 1970 September 10 (Box 6)
  - P-346, Carson Labs, Holographic diocument retrieval system, Declined 1970 December 10 (Box 6)
  - P-347, University of Connecticut, Marine materials laboratory, declined 1970 November 12 (Box 6)
  - P-348, University of Connecticut, Nitrogen oxide emissions, Declined 1970 November 12 (Box 6)
  - P-349, Yale University, Contamination of trees & shrubs, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-350, CBS Labs, Reanalysis of noise data, Declined 1971 January 11 (Box 6)
  - P-351, Eastern Connecticut State College, Puerto Rican parents and children, Granted 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-352, IFF, Technology assessment, Withdrawn 1971 January 5 (Box 6)
  - P-353, University of Connecticut, Ternary transition metal oxides, Granted (partial supp.) 1970 November 12 (Box 6)
  - P-354, Development Commission, Defense conversion system, Granted 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-355, University of Connecticut, Mass unemployment in Connecticut, Declined 1970 October 27 (Box 6)
  - P-356, Rowland Development Corp., Materials for highway safety, Declined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-357, Yale University, Coherent optics laboratory, Declined 1970 December 10 (Box 6)
  - P-358, IFF, Future of drug abuse in Connecticut, Deferred action 1970 December 10, Declined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-359, CEM, Study of the Connecticut coastline, Declined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-360, Mueller Assoc., Use of energy from solid waste, Declined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-361, NERAC, Computer search tapes (Box 6)
  - P-362, Yale University, Spectroscopic studies of crystals, Deferred, 1971 January 11 (Box 6)
  - P-363, Yale University, Research laboratories at Southbury, Declined 1970 December 10 (Box 6)
  - P-364, Meyers Electro/Cooling Products, Advanced solid waste disposal techniques, Granter 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-365, University of Bridgeport, Upper triassic dinosaurs (Box 6)
  - P-366, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Managing technical innovation, Declined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-367, University of Bridgeport, Ecological study of Housatonic River, 1971 January 15 (Box 6)
  - P-368, Mental Health Dept., Adolescent drug culture, Decllined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-369, University of Connecticut, Annealing & drawing of polymers, Granted 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-370, University of Connecticut, Interferometric infrared spectrometer (Box 6)
  - P-371, University of Connecticut, Marine research program for Long Island Sound (Box 6)
  - P-372, New England Institute, Organic superconduction, Declined 1971 January 14 (Box 6)
  - P-373, Mental Health Dept., Matching of clients & treatments, Declined 1971 January 11 (Box 6)
  - P-374, University of Connecticut, Chonic plumbism (Box 6)
  - P-375, Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Nitric oxide kinetics (Box 6)
  - P-376, Yale University, Laser-Raman analysis of air pollutants (Box 6)
  - P-377, Wesleyan University, The Josephson effect (Box 6)
  - P-378, Ebony Businessmen's League, Minority-owned businesses, Deferred 1971 January 11 (Box 6)
  - P-379, Regional Planning Agency of South Central Connecticut, Municipal housing development (Box 7)
  - P-380, Wesleyan University, Magnetism in alloy systems (Box 7)
  - P-381, TRC, Data processing & small business (Box 7)
  - P-382, URIC, Metric conversion (Box 7)
  - P-373, Yale University, Enzyme evolution (Box 7)
  - P-384, Connecticut State Labor Council AFL-CIO, Drop-outs from apprentice training program, Granted 1971 January 11 (Box 7)
  - P-385, Windward Oceanography Institute, Ecology of blue crab (Box 7)
  - P-386, University of Connecticut, Tectonophysics related to orogens (Box 7)
  - P-387, University of Connecticut, Micro-economic study of environmental problem (Box 7)
  - P-388, University of Connecticut, Effect of proteolytic enzymes (Box 7)
  - P-389, Yale University, Isotope separation in crossed jets (Box 7)
  - P-390, University of Connecticut, Treatment of sickle cell anemia (Box 7)
  - P-391, Urban Research & Development Corp., Solid waste research facility (Box 7)
- Series 2. Research support award (RSA) files, 1965-1971
  Arranged by year and thereuynder numerically.
  No list has been received, but the list of "proposals" is a guide and the proposal folders contain cross references to the award files.
  - 66-1 - 66-8, 67-1 - 67-2 (Box 8)
  - 67-3 - 67-8 (Box 9)
  - 67-9 - 67-18, 68-1 - 68-4 (Box 10)
  - 68-5 - 68-15 (Box 11)
  - 68-16 - 68-26 (Box 12)
  - 68-27 - 68-38, 69-1 (Box 13)
  - 69-2 - 69-10 (Box 14)
  - 69-11 - 69-16, 70-1 - 70-4 (Box 15)
  - 70-5 - -70-16 (Box 16)
  - 70-18 - 70-28, 71-2 - 71-5 (Box 17)
  - 71-16 - 71-22 (Box 18)
- Series 3. Student research support award (SRSA) files, 1971
  - Student research (Box 19)
  - 71-01, Wesleyan University (Box 19)
  - 71-02, Connecticut College (Box 19)
  - 71-03, University of Connecticut (Box 19)
  - 71-04, Southern Connecticut State College (Box 19)
  - 71-05, Central Connecticut State College (Box 19)
  - 71-06, University of Hartford (Box 19)
  - 71-07, Eastern Connecticut State College (Box 19)
  - 71-08, Trinity College (Box 19)
  - 71-09, Quinnipiac College (Box 19)
  - 71-10, Yale University (Box 19)
  - 71-11, Sacred Heart University (Box 19)
  - 71-12, Fairfield University (Box 19)
  - 71-13, Albrertus Magnus College (Box 19)
  - 71-14, St. Joseph College (Box 19)
  - 71-15, University of Bridgeport (Box 19)
  - 71-16, Western Connecticut State College (Box 19)
- Series 4. Contract files, 1965-1971
  - CBS Laboratories (Box 20)
  - Arthur D. Little, Inc. (Box 20-21)
  - International Business Machines (Box 21)
  - Meyers Electrocooling Products, Inc. (Box 21-22)
  - James S. Mirges & Associates (Box 22)
  - The New England Economic Research Foundation (Eastern Regional Conference) (Box 22)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (Box 22)
  - Wilbur Smith and Associates (Box 22-23)
  - Soros Associates (Box 23)
  - Travelers Research Center, Inc. (Box 24)
  - University Research Institute of Connecticut (Box 24)
  - State Techinical Services Contracts (Box 25)
- Series 5. Minutes of meetings, 1965-1970
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Records, 1965 October-1970 December (Box 26)
- Series 6. Memoranda from Director to Commission members, 1966-1970
  - Records, 1966 April-1970 December (Box 27)
- Series 7. Reading files, 1966-1971
  Arranged alphabetically for the most part by staff member and thereunder chronologically.
  - Burlew, John S.
    - 1966 May-1969 February (Box 28)
    - 1969 March-1971 July (Box 29)
  - Battalino, Susan W., 1969-1970 (Box 29)
  - Britt, Eileen H., 1967-1968 (Box 29)